Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. 16mm microfilm Treasurer's Office records, 1916-1949 and undated RL.11720
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Lawsuits, Claims, Court Orders, Judgments, etc., 1927-1944 and undated; 5
  - Lever--Fred Morgan claim, 1933 (Reel 66)
    See reel 81, claims; reel 88, signed releases
  - Libby McNeil & Libby--Jeffrey Heiman "Handbook for Americans", 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Lorillard--Richardson and Bliss files, 1940-1941 (Reel 248)
  - Lorillard--Sylvan Levin claim, 1944 (Reel 248)
  - Lost painting, Phoenix, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Major Bowes v. Philco Radio & Television, 1936 (Reel 86)
  - Marjorie Allen, undated (Reel 128)
  - Martin Ullman Studios v. JWT, 1931-1933 (Reel 66)
  - Melvin Woodworth, 1932 (Reel 248)
  - Miller Montague v. Donovan, 1939-1940 (Reel 86)
  - New York Dress Institute--Complaint from B. Altman on "Basic" dress, 1941 (Reel 249)
  - New York Dress Institute--Dress stain, loss, 1941 (Reel 249)
  - New York Times v. Gus D. Nations, 1931 (Reel 87)
  - Northam Warren (Cutex)--Mr. Lynn of Marshall Drug regarding use of his store in ads, 1943 (Reel 248)
  - Northam Warren Canada, 1937-1938 (Reel 248)
  - Old Colony Club, undated (Reel 88)
  - Old JWT legal papers, undated (Reel 88)
  - Pacific Coast, 1938-1939 (Reel 248)
  - Permission to do business in the State of Missouri, 1930-1938 (Reel 86)
  - Permission to do business in the State of Missouri, 1930-1938 (Reel 87)
  - Pond's--agreement regarding Stanley Holt work on Fraser & Best problem, 1931 (Reel 88)
  - Pond's--Greta Keller, 1932 (Reel 88)
  - Pond's--Larry Van Orden, Anne Nissen claim, "She's Engaged" ad, 1942-1943 (Reel 248)
  - RCA--Harry Delson "What's New" claim, 1943 (Reel 248)
  - Richard Cantillon, undated (Reel 128)
  - Rush Jermon, undated (Reel 128)
  - Scott Paper--Therese Liedtke claim (baby's photo for Waldorf tissue), 1943 (Reel 248)
  - Shell Oil, 1932 and undated (Reel 88)
  - Shell Oil-- R.W. Luce material, 1939-1940 (Reel 66)
  - Shell Oil--Cosmo Di Selvo claim, "Oranges into Pineapples", 1943 (Reel 248)
  - Shell Oil--Edward Evans claim, "Ground Crew" campaign, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Shell Oil--Good Old Summertime, 1937 (Reel 66)
  - Shell Oil--Marks Music, 1937 (Reel 248)
  - Shell Oil--Michelson v. Shell Oil, 1937-1940 (Reel 66)
    See reels 78, 85, 194
  - Shell Oil--Radio program, Al Jolson use of Harry Savoy copyright material, 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Shell Oil--Samuel Criden's objection to use of "Yoo Hoo I'm an Indian" by Fannie Brice, 1936 (Reel 66)
  - Shell Oil--Scott Howe Bowen, 1932 (Reel 66)
  - Shell Oil--Summit Hotel v. NBC, 1940 (Reel 248)
  - Shell Radio Program--Summit Hotel v. NBC and Al Jolson, 1935-1941 (Reel 66)
  - ShellOil--Photostats of material sent to Winfield Taylor by Richard Luce (ideas for Shell), 1939 (Reel 88)
  - Simmons--Letter from Theodore Roosevelt, undated (Reel 88)
  - Sstandard Brands, 1932-1937 (Reel 88)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--Bundy & Schloss, 1938 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--Cady claims, 1939 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--de River claim, 1938 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--Eddie Cantor program, use of Edna Ferber material "All the World's a Stage", 1934 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--Knox claim "Londonderry Air", 1937-1939 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Chase & Sanborn)--Matt Brooks claim, 1939 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Christine Inglis claim, 1927 (Reel 66)
    See reel 88, releases
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Edward S. Coleman claim, Let's Dance book, 1937 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Joe Baker broadcast, alleged use of J.K.Watson copyright material, 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Milton Herbert Groper claim, 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Radio program "Twentieth Century", 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Reis & Dunn use of "The Music Box", 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands (Fleischmann)--Roy Smeck imitation of Bill Robinson's dance routine, 1935 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Arlene Lovengreen claim, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Standard Brands--Barney Gerard claim, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Standard Brands--Bert Bertrand, Abbot & Costello, 1941 (Reel 249)
  - Standard Brands--Betty Fearing suit, 1930-1932 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Conklin v. Standard Brands, 1937 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Dr. Kilmer's Swamp, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Standard Brands--Elsa Maxwell's Agent Lee through Lawyer Gerstein, 1944 (Reel 248)
  - Standard Brands--Gannon Kearin claim of idea, Vox Pop, 1936 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Gutt v. Standard Brands, 1937-1938 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Helen Gutt, 1938 (Reel 248)
  - Standard Brands--Howard Trafton claim, 1938 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Jerry Cady, 1929 (Reel 248)
  - Standard Brands--Joe Cook and Theo Schreiber, 1938 (Reel 248)
  - Standard Brands--Life v. Eddie Cantor, NBC and Standard Brands, 1934 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Major Bowes Amateur Magazine, 1936 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Mrs. Lloyd Thanhouser claim, 1932 (Reel 66)
  - Standard Brands--Rudy Vallee Show, Alberto Casella (Death Takes a Holiday) claim, connection with broadcast of "Mr. James Changes His Mind", 1937 (Reel 128)
  - Standard Brands--Storm v. We, undated (Reel 70)
  - Standard Brands--Weissmuller-Holm swim book, 1940 (Reel 249)
  - Standard Brands--Will Stanton claim, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Statesbury v. Fowler (see Gus Fowler), undated (Reel 87)
  - Stephen Itzenhauser, undated (Reel 128)
  - Swift, 1936-1940 (Reel 88)
  - Swift--"Three Squares a Day" claim, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Swift--A. Zamouzakis, 1937 (Reel 248)
  - Swift--Harry Sickles, 1936 (Reel 248)
  - Swift--Little Boy Blue, 1936 (Reel 66)
  - Swift--Lost photographs, 1942 (Reel 249)
  - Swift--Stebbins Boys, Henry Fisk Carlton, 1932-1939 (Reel 66)
  - Textron--Mrs. Dora De Vries claim, payment for art works, 1943 (Reel 248)
  - Tower Magazines, 1934-1935 (Reel 128)
  - Tower Magazines, 1934-1935 (Reel 248)
    Bankruptcy, see also reel 128; material sent to U.S. Attorney Horney at court house, Foley Square, New York
  - Westheimer v. General Mills, 1939 (Reel 66)
  - William Adams, undated (Reel 128)
  - William Esty, 1931-1932, 1934 (Reel 86)
  - William Morris Agency v. Tom Howard, undated (Reel 73)
    From reel 70
  - Woodworth case, 1928-1937 (Reel 248)
    Mr. Resor's papers; see reel 78 for Mr. Wilson's papers; reel 88 for release
  - Woodworth case, undated (Reel 78)
  - Woodworth case, undated (Reel 88)
  - Woodworth suit, 1931-1940 (Reel 87)
- Old Releases, Lux, 1930-1939 and undated; 6
  - Ada Leonard, 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Al Greenwood, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Andrea Leeds, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Anita Kerry, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Anita Louise, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Ann Dvorak, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Arch Reeve, Paramount Pictures, 1929 (Reel 249)
  - Barbara Newberry, 1930 (Reel 249)
  - Barbara Read, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Betty Compton, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Blanche Sweet, 1931 (Reel 249)
  - Busby Berkeley, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Carol Stone, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Cary Grant, undated (Reel 249)
  - Clara Bow, undated (Reel 249)
  - Constance Bennett, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Dolores Costillo Barrymore, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Dolores Del Rio, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Dorothy Dell, undated (Reel 249)
  - Dorothy Jordan, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Eddie Cantor, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Editorial and Plan Department, London, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Enid Bennett, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Esther Ralston, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Ethel Merman, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Ethel Shutta, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Fay Wray, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Forrest Theatre, W. Dilton, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Gertrude Omstead, undated (Reel 249)
  - Ginger Rogers, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Gladys Swarthout, 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Grace Lord, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Grace Moore, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - H. Wendy Barrie, undated (Reel 249)
  - Harriet Hillard, undated (Reel 249)
  - Helen Morgan, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - James and Deanna Durbin, 1937 (Reel 249)
  - Jane Withers and mother, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Janet Gaynor, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Janet Henle, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Jannette A. MacDonald, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Joan Bennet, undated (Reel 249)
  - Joan Blondell, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Joan Blondell, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Joan Blondell, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Joseph Whitcomb, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - June Clyde, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Kathleen Edwards, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Kay Sutton, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Leona Maricle, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Loretta Young, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Mabel Tode, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Margaret Irving, undated (Reel 249)
  - Margaret Lindsay, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Margaret Perry, 1930 (Reel 249)
  - Margaret Sullavan, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Margaret Sullavan, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Marjorie Gatson, undated (Reel 249)
  - Mary Astor, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Mary Forbes, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - Maurice Chevalier, 1935 (Reel 249)
  - May Robson, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Merle Oberon, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Mildred Keats, 1930 (Reel 249)
  - Molly Lamont, undated (Reel 249)
  - Nancy Carroll, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Odett Mythil, undated (Reel 249)
  - Patricia Morison, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Rocbelle Hudson and mother, 1936 (Reel 249)
  - Rosalind Keith, undated (Reel 249)
  - Rosalind Russell, 1939 (Reel 249)
  - Rosina Lawrence, undated (Reel 249)
  - Ruby Keeler, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Sally Eilers, 1934 (Reel 249)
  - Sally Pond, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Simone French, undated (Reel 249)
  - Sophie Tucker, 1938 (Reel 249)
  - Una O'Connor, undated (Reel 249)
  - Valerie Taylor, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Verree Teasdale, 1932 (Reel 249)
  - Virginia Weidler, Mrs. Margaret Weidler, undated (Reel 249)
  - Waldorf Theatre, Harry Nelmes, 1933 (Reel 249)
  - Wallace Ford, 1933 (Reel 249)
- Signed Estimates, 1938-1949; 7
  - American League Baseball, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - American Weekly, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - American Weekly, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - American Weekly, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - American Weekly, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - American Weekly, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - American Weekly, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Anthracite Industries, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Anthracite Industries, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Anthracite Industries, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Anthracite Industries, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Anthracite Industries, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Ariston, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Arthur Rhodes, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Associated Hospital Service, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Atlantic Petroleum, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Atlantic Union Committee, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Atlantis Sales, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Auckland Power Board, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Ballantine, 1943 (Reel 751)
  - Ballantine, 1943 (Reel 752)
  - Ballantine, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Ballantine, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Ballantine, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Ballantine, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Ballantine, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Ballantine, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Baur Brothers Bakery, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Baur Brothers Bakery, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Block Drug, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Blue Cross, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Blue Cross, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Blue Cross, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Blue Cross, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Brewing Industry Foundation, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Bridgeport Thermostat, 1944 (Reel 753)
  - Bridgeport Thermostat, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Brillo, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Brillo, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Brillo, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Brillo, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Brillo, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Brillo, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - British Export Association, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Bruno-New York, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Bureau of Land Management, U.S. Dept. of Interior, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Burroughs Adding Machine, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Buxton, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Buxton, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Buxton, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Buxton, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Buxton, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Buxton, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Calsodent, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Carreras (Craven A cigarettes), 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Carter's Ink, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Carter's Ink, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Carter's Ink, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Carter's Ink, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Carter's Ink, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Carter's Ink, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Carter's Products, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Carter's Products, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Caterpillar, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Chesebrough, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Chesebrough, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Chesebrough, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Chesebrough, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Church & Dwight, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Citizens' Committee for Reorganization of Executive Branch of the Government, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Clifford Baker Jr., 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Coal Consumers Protective Association, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Cristais Prado, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Devoe & Raynolds, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Division of Nurse Education, USPHS, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Douglas Aircraft, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - E.G. Burke (Guinness), 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Eastern Anglia, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Elgin Watch, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Elgin Watch, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Equitable Life Assurance, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - F. W. Fitch, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - F.W. Fitch, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - F.W. Fitch, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Fanny Farmer, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Farrell Lines, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Finch Junior College, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Ford Dealer, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Ford Dealer, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Ford Dealer, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Ford Dealer Somerville, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Ford Dealers, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Ford Edgewater, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Ford Motor, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Ford Motor, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Ford Motor, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Ford Motor, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Ford Motor, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Ford Pittsburgh, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Ford Radio, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Fred Astaire Dance Studios, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Fred Astaire Dance Studios, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Fulton Sylphon, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Fulton Sylphon, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Gallowhur Chemical, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - General Cigar, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - General Cigar, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - General Cigar, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - General Cigar, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - General Cigar, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - General Cigar, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Gillette Advertising, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Gillette Safety Razor, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Gillette Safety Razor, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Gillette Safety Razor, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Gillette Safety Razor, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Gillette Safety Razor, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Glasco Products, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Glasco Products, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Glass Container Manufacturers Institute, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Guinness, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Guinness, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Guinness, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Guinness, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Gutenberghus Reklambureau, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Hartogs, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Holdart, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Horlicks, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Horlicks, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Institute of Life Insurance, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Irving Trust, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Irving Trust, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Irving Trust, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Irving Trust, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Irving Trust, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Irving Trust, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - J. Walter Thompson, 1949 (Reel 872)
  - J.B. Williams, 1944 (Reel 756)
  - J.B. Williams, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - J.B. Williams, 1946 (Reel 761)
  - J.B. Williams, 1947 (Reel 764)
  - J.B. Williams, 1948 (Reel 768)
  - James A. Jobling & Co., 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Johns-Manville, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Johns-Manville, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Johns-Manville, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Johns-Manville, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Johns-Manville, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Johns-Manville, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Johns-Manville, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Johnson & Johnson, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Joint Queensview Housing Enterprises, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Kellogg, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Kellogg, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Kellogg, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Kellogg, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Kellogg, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Kodak, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Kodak, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Kodak, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Kodak, 1947 (Reel 761)
  - Kodak, 1948 (Reel 764)
  - Kodak, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Kodak, 1949 (Reel 868)
  - Kraft, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Kraft, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Kraft, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Kraft, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Kraft, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Kraft (Foreign), 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Kroy, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Kroy Processors, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Kroy Unshrinkable Wools, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - L.D. Seymour, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - L.D. Seymour, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - L.D. Seymour, 1948 (Reel 767)
  - L.D. Seymour, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Lamont Corliss, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Lamont Corliss, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Lamont Corliss, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Lamont Corliss, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Lamont Corliss, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Lever Brothers, 1942-1943 (Reel 751)
  - Lever Brothers, 1945 (Reel 756)
  - Lever Brothers, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Lever Brothers, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Lever Brothers, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Libby McNeil & Libby, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Linden Hill (John Robert Powers course), 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Lober Brothers, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Lorillard (Old Gold), 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Lux Flakes, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Lux Flakes, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Lux Flakes, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Lux Flakes, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Lux Flakes, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Lux Soap, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Lux Soap, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Lux Toilet Soap, 1943 (Reel 752)
  - Lux Toilet Soap, 1943 (Reel 753)
  - Lux Toilet Soap, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Lux Toilet Soap, 1948 (Reel 765)
  - Mentholatum, 1944 (Reel 754)
  - Mentholatum, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Mentholatum, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Mentholatum, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Mentholatum, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Mentholatum, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Mentholatum, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Milldale, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Morilla, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Nashua Manufacturing, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Nashua Manufacturing, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Nashua Mills (Textron), 1949 (Reel 870)
  - National Fisheries Institute, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - National Fisheries Institute, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - National Peanut Council, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - NBC, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - NBC, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - NBC, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - NBC, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - NBC, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - NBC, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - New Holland Machine, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - New York Dress Institute, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - New York Subways Advertising, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - New York Subways Advertising, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - New York Subways Advertising, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - New York Subways Advertising, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - New York Subways Advertising, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - New York Times, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - New York Yankees, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - New York Yankees, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - New York Yankees, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Newport News Shipbuilding & Dry Dock Co., 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Northam Warren (Odorono, Cutex), 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Northam Warren (Odorono, Cutex), 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Northam Warren (Odorono, Cutex), 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Northam Warren (Odorono, Cutex), 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Northrop Aircraft, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Northrop Aircraft, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Northrop Aircraft, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Omega Watch, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Omega Watch, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Oneida, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Oneida, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Owens-Illinois Glass, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Oxford University Press, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Oxford University Press, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Oxford University Press, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Oxford University Press, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Pan Am, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Pan Am, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Pan Am, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Pan Am, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Pan Am, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Pan Am, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Parker Pen, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Parker Pen, 1947 (Reel 762)
  - Parker Pen, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Parker Pen, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Parker Pen, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Parker Pen (Foreign), 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Parker Pen (Foreign), 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Penick & Ford, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Penick & Ford, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Penick & Ford, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Penick & Ford, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Penick & Ford, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Penick & Ford, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airlines, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airlines, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Pennsylvania Central Airlines, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Pepsodent, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Pharma-Craft, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Planters Peanuts, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Pond's, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Pond's, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Pond's, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Pond's, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Pond's, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Pond's, 1949 (Reel 870)
  - Pond's, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Pruna Commercial and Industrial Publicity, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - Pruna Commercial and Industrial Publicity, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Pruna Ltd., 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Purolator, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - R.T. French, 1949 (Reel 869)
  - Radio Times, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Radiomarine, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Radiomarine, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Radiomarine, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Radiomarine, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - RCA, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - RCA, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - RCA, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - RCA Institutional and Engineering, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - RCA Institutional and Engineering, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1946 (Reel 759)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - RCA Victor Division, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Reader's Digest, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Reader's Digest, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Reader's Digest, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Reader's Digest (Foreign), 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Reader's Digest (Foreign), 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Republican Fusion Party, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Reynolds Metals, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Rheem, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Rheem, 1945 (Reel 757)
  - Robert Benson-Boen Manufacturing, 1946 (Reel 758)
  - Rototiller, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Rystan, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Rystan, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Rystan, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Rystan, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Rystan, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Sarfert Hosiery Mills, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Sarfert Hosiery Mills, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Scott & Grauer, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Scott Paper, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Scott Paper, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Scott Paper, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Scott Paper, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Scott Paper, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Scott Paper, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Scranton Lace, 1944 (Reel 755)
  - Scranton Lace, 1945 (Reel 758)
  - Scranton Lace, 1946 (Reel 760)
  - Scranton Lace, 1947 (Reel 763)
  - Scranton Lace, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Scranton Lace, 1949 (Reel 871)
  - Sears Roebuck, 1948 (Reel 766)
  - Sears Roebuck, 1949 (Reel 871)